Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
Why are you doing this you traitor
because it's what I believe is right?
I envy you.
Finger pistol.
Did you write down your wish yet?
Time to light up the skyboats!
Wowie!
All right, let's fly it!
Looks like it's time to send
your wish to the heavens.
You ready, Daddy?
All right, now come, come!
He's bending the earth of his attacks.
Is that carnivish from the palace?
How is that possible?
You won't show mercy! Fine!
Let's see how you handle this!
Please don't believe me!
Ow!
Don't tell me you're so close!
You're not the only one who can
predict people's attacks, you know.
I'll even copy your technique.
How do you like that?
Damn it!
He ate me!
Let me out of here!
I said let me out!
Blast breath!
Form a Bounce Man!
That scaly bastard!
He's feeding the crap out of me!
Gotta turn this around!
You're coming back for more, are you?
He's gotta be running
out of steam after that!
Once fourth gear wears off, I'm done for!
I'm running out of time to finish him off!
All right, fourth gear, don't fail me now!
Not again!
Never thought those rubber powers of
yours would give me so much trouble!
Looks like you're about done, though.
Quiet!
Never done!
Let's enjoy the finale, Straw Hat.
Shut up!
I said I'm not here to have fun.
I'm here to beat you!
I've seen what you've done to Wano.
They can't even find water to drink.
Or enough food to eat.
Not as long as you're here!
They have nothing, because
they lost the battle to me.
You should thank me for
letting them keep their lives.
Side with who you like, but
the people of Wano are losers.
Worse yet, they've grown
accustomed to being losers.
The weak bow down and the
honorable die over and over.
I've watched them make pathetic
excuses for their failures.
Shut your mouth.
You have no idea how
strong the samurai are.
Are they strong or are they acting strong?
True strength doesn't require praise.
It speaks for itself.
Are you the real thing
or not? It's time.
to find out.
No, go, no!
Overcome
Dying!
Not.
Done.
Yet.
Gotta make sure he's down for good!
Oh dear, it's gonna run
out on me any second now!
Thunder Meadow!
Barbara!
I don't know.
one shot it's time to
finish up the story i'm
betting everything i've got
on this All right, Brat,
show me!
Win or lose, this is the end!
You're gonna fail this one!
C .P. Zero.
Why is he here?
Oh, my God.
I don't know. I
don't
know.
I can't hear it.
Luffy's voice is gone.
The battle on the rooftop
has come to an end.
The winner, Kaido, King of the Beasts.
Do you know what you've done?
I'll kill you!
Kawamatsu!
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
We need to evacuate now!
I cannot flee when thousands of our
comrades are still in the castle!
We have to make it home together, but
we're too high up to reach the seawater!
Is there nothing we can
do to stop this fire?
Everyone, run to safety!
There's no honor in burning to death!
What? Last breath?
Wait, is that...?
Kaido.
Where is your leader?
Bring Odin's son to me?
It's time for Momonosuke
to announce his surrender.
Straw Hat Luffy is dead.
What did he just say?
Straw Hat's voice went
silent, so it's true.
Seems he was no match for an emperor.
You're lying.
You have to be lying.
Lucy would never, he would never.
No, Lucy is dead!
If any of you still have the
courage to defy me and step up,
I haven't had my fill of
violence for the night.
Still hang out with a silver
skin in the commander Tino's way!
Come back, big bro!
You can't die now!
You just can't!
Hey stop are you crazy i
won't let him keep lying?
Who does that snake think he's fooling?
He's a liar and i won't
let him get away with it.
You say luffy's dead you think
we'll just believe you're stupid?
lies and give up?
When Luffy says he'll win,
he'll do it no matter what.
He will never
lose, do you hear me?
And he will not die.
He can't die.
You're a liar.
Well, now that's
more like it.
At least one of you
has some guts. Shut up.
Since you don't seem to understand,
Allow me to teach you
the meaning of defeat.
Last prayer!
Get back!
Bunami, are you okay?
You need to pull it together.
The battle's not over yet.
Lucy.
Or a gushing of the land
on the flower capital.
And I will take control
of the land of Wano.
Orochi has been too lenient on you.
I'll show you true suffering.
This country will be my weapons factory.
And all men.
Women and children will be my slaves.
When you're too exhausted
to work, roll over and die.
Every time we lose a slave,
we'll just replace it.
My wrath is the price you
pay for your defiance.
This is what happens
when you lose a battle.
Your life belongs to the victor.
Your hopes and dreams are mine
to trample, However I please.
Bring Momonosuke here.
I'll continue to slaughter
until that happens.
Your country is finished.
Your children and your children's
children will sink into despair.
That is the cost of your weakness.
No, not my family.
Don't do this, please.
Hey, look over there.
Kid-in-law are barely alive.
Let's butcher them while they're down.
It doesn't matter if you took out Big Mom.
You are never going to be Commander Daddy.
You took your own dream.
I hope you're happy.
Little shits.
Protect the captains!
I don't what's he doing here?
Let's go!
Okay
Yeah
Everywhere
Isn't there a way out?
You still got some fight
left in you, Trafalgar?
Because I'm not going to
sit here and wait to die.
Damn it, Straw Hats.
Have you gone mad?
We can't possibly win now.
How can we hope to succeed
when even Luffy failed?
We have to live until we die!
We'll put our lives on the
line until we breathe our last!
Just as Samurai should!
If we don't do it, then who else will?
Our allies are wounded right now.
But so is Kaido!
This might be our chance!
Yamato, this is absurd!
Kaido is an emperor of the sea!
We underestimated his strength!
It's as simple as that!
Victory is no longer within our reach.
If we continue to resist, it
will only result in more deaths.
We did our best, but it
simply wasn't enough.
I know this is difficult to
hear, but Luffy has lost.
We have no choice but to surrender.
No, I will never allow that!
I won't live as a slave!
You think there's value in that?
Living your life in chains waiting to die?
You don't even know that
surrendering will save anyone!
I won't allow it!
I'll stop you myself!
The daimyo who stood up to
Orochi died hungry for revenge,
but they never gave up on this country!
We've inherited its future,
and we carry the weight of all the
dreams that they couldn't fulfill!
I won't surrender.
And even if you and I die here
tonight, at least we'll die together!
Momonosuke...
Momonosuke, I can hear them.
It's been so long
Zonesia, what are you talking about?
I can hear the drums of liberation.
For the first time in 800 years!
He is here!
I'm sure of it!
Who is here?
Joy Boy has returned!